[
    {
      "question":"1.Which testing is done by developer?",
      "Option a":"a.Unit Testing",
      "Option b":"b.Integration Testing",
      "Option c":"c.Sanity Testing",
      "Option d":"d.Regression Testing",
      "answer":"a"
    },
    {

      "question":"2.Which is functional testing?",
      "Option a":"a.Load Testing",
      "Option b":"b.Security Testing",
      "Option c":"c.Gorilla Testing",
      "Option d":"d.Benchmark Testing",
      "answer":"c"
    },
    {

      "question":"3.Which term is used to define testing?",
      "Option a":"a.Evaluating deliverable to find errors",
      "Option b":"b.Finding broken code",
      "Option c":"c.A stage of all projects",
      "Option d":"d.None of the above",
      "answer":"a"
    },
    {
      "question":"4.Which methodology is used to performed Maintenance testing?",
      "Option a":"a.Breadth test and depth test",
      "Option b":"b.Confirmation testing",
      "Option c":"c.Retesting",
      "Option d":"d.Sanity testing",
      "answer":"a"
    },
    {

      "question":"5.Which of the following is not part of the Test document?",
      "Option a":"a.Test Case",
      "Option b":"b.Requirements Traceability Matrix [RTM]",
      "Option c":"c.Test strategy",
      "Option d":"d.Project Initiation Note [PIN]",
      "answer":"d"
    },
    {

      "question":"6.Which of the following is not a valid phase of SDLC (Software Development Life Cycle)?",
      "Option a":"a.Testing Phase",
      "Option b":"b.Requirement Phase",
      "Option c":"c.Deployment phase",
      "Option d":"d.Testing closure",
      "answer":"d"
    },
    {

      "question":"7.Which of the following testing is also known as white-box testing?",
      "Option a":"a.Structural testing",
      "Option b":"b.Error guessing technique",
      "Option c":"c.Design based testing",
      "Option d":"d.None of the above",
      "answer":"a"
    },
    {

      "question":"8.Which of the following testing is related to the boundary value analysis?",
      "Option a":"a.White box and black box testing",
      "Option b":"b.White-box testing",
      "Option c":"c.Black box testing",
      "Option d":"d.None of the above",
      "answer":"c"
    },
    {

      "question":"9.Functional testing is a ?",
      "Option a":"a.Test design technique",
      "Option b":"b.Test level",
      "Option c":"c.SDLC Model",
      "Option d":"d.Test type",
      "answer":"d"
    },
    {

      "question":"10.What are the different levels of Testing?",
      "Option a":"a.Integration testing",
      "Option b":"b.Unit testing",
      "Option c":"c.System testing",
      "Option d":"d.All of the above",
      "answer":"d"
    },
    {

      "question":"11.Sanity testing is a ------",
      "Option a":"a.Test type",
      "Option b":"b.Test Execution Level",
      "Option c":"c.Test Level",
      "Option d":"d.Test design technique",
      "answer":"b"
    },
    {

      "question":"12.White box testing techniques are?",
      "Option a":"a.Statement coverage testing",
      "Option b":"b.Decision coverage testing",
      "Option c":"c.Data flow testing",
      "Option d":"d.All of the above",
      "answer":"d"
    },
    {

      "question":"13.In which environment we can performed the Alpha testing?",
      "Option a":"a.User's end",
      "Option b":"b.Developer's end",
      "Option c":"c.User's and developer's end",
      "Option d":"d.None of the above",
      "answer":"b"
    },
    {

      "question":"14.Which of the below is not a part of the Test Plan?",
      "Option a":"a.Schedule",
      "Option b":"b.Risk",
      "Option c":"c.Incident reports",
      "Option d":"d.Entry and exit criteria",
      "answer":"c"
    },
    {

      "question":"15.What is the key objective of Integration testing?",
      "Option a":"a.Design Errors",
      "Option b":"b.Interface Errors",
      "Option c":"c.Procedure Errors",
      "Option d":"d.None of the mentioned",
      "answer":"b"
    },
    {

      "question":"16.Exploratory testing is a -----?",
      "Option a":"a.Experience-based Test Design Technique",
      "Option b":"b.White Box Test Design Technique",
      "Option c":"c.Black Box Test Design Technique",
      "Option d":"d.Grey Box Test Design Technique",
      "answer":"a"
    },
    {

      "question":"17.What is the best time to perform Regression testing?",
      "Option a":"a.After the software has been modified",
      "Option b":"b.As frequently as possible",
      "Option c":"c.When the environment has been modified",
      "Option d":"d.Both option a & c",
      "answer":"d"
    },
    {

      "question":"18.Which of the following is not part of the Test type?",
      "Option a":"a.Function testing",
      "Option b":"b.System testing",
      "Option c":"c.Statement testing",
      "Option d":"d.Database testing",
      "answer":"c"
    },
    {

      "question":"19.Which Test Document is used to define the Exit Criteria of Testing?",
      "Option a":"a.Defect Report",
      "Option b":"b.Test Summary Report",
      "Option c":"c.Test Case",
      "Option d":"d.Test Plan",
      "answer":"d"
    },
    {

      "question":"20.Which testing technique is used for usability testing?",
      "Option a":"a.Exit Criteria",
      "Option b":"b.How much regression testing should be done?",
      "Option c":"c.Different Tools to perform Regression Testing",
      "Option d":"d.How many more test cases need to write?",
      "answer":"b"
    }
  ]